

## **Summary**

Passionate n' well-qualified mobile engineer with advanced skills on Flutter. Studying Agile, Clean Architecture, SOLID, TDD, Design Patterns and Refactoring. I'm committed to the best way to produce high-quality softwares following good principles and techniques. I have more than 3 years of related experience with software development.

# Favorite technologies



# **Employment history**

Mobile developer at Megaleios June 2021 - August 2021

Mobile developer at Bean Softwares
March 2021 - June 2021

Mobile developer at Thalamus Digital July 2020 - June 2021

Mobile developer at MFIT Personal January 2020 - May 2020

#### Education

Computer Science at Univali February 2020 - Present

English at KNN Idiomas September 2020 - Present

# **Projects**

Entrepreneur at Pineapple August 2021 - Present A personal budget planner.

Entrepreneur at iCut
May 2021 - Present
A barber appointment app.

Voluntary coding instructor May 2021 - August 2021 Teaching some friends how to code.

Entrepreneur at StudentPlus
August 2018 - April 2021
A study planner based on the Pomodoro technique.

#### **Details**

Itajaí, SC, Brazil contact@lucasbatista.me

### Links

LinkedIn

GitHub

WhatsApp

Website

### Skills

**TDD** 

Refactoring

Clean Architecture

**SOLID** 

Design Patterns

DevOps

**UML** 

Agile

# Languages

English

#### **Hobbies**

Hackathons, pair programming, teaching, code kata and reading.